Adam McKenna

Full Stack Developer

I like building useful products that people actually enjoy using.

I'm a full stack developer focused on **React**, **TypeScript**, and **Node.js** — comfortable across the stack, and committed to writing **clean code** and delivering **rich**, **accessible user experiences**.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Track24

Dec 2024 - Present - London, UK (Remote)

Developed and maintained *AtlasNXT*, a duty-of-care platform used by organisations including the BBC, UN and FCDO.

Tech: Elixir (Phoenix), React.js, TypeScript, TailwindCSS, Mapbox.js

Full Stack Developer

Binary Vision

Aug 2022 - Mar 2023 - London, UK

Delivered *Oi View*, a data visualisation platform commissioned by Oxford Instruments to analyse scientific output from microscope detectors.

Tech: React (Next.js), TypeScript, Node.js, react-spring

Senior Frontend Developer

DWP Digital (UK Gov't)

Apr 2021 - Oct 2021 - Sheffield/Manchester, UK

Built and maintained authentication and admin tools for internal and public-facing use by DWP agents and benefit recipients.

Tech: React, Node.js, GOV.UK Design System, ForgeRock

Full Stack Developer

Money Advice Trust

Jan 2020 - Apr 2021 - Birmingham, UK

Led the rebuild and relaunch of 3 websites for a UK debt-support charity, delivering increased performance, accessibility and reach.

Tech: React (Gatsby.js, Next.js), Django (Python), Stencil.js

Frontend Developer

Namics GmbH

Sep 2018 - Nov 2019 - Frankfurt am Main, Germany

Delivered *Analytics Unlocked*, a global marketing analytics dashboard for Siemens, helping teams analyse and optimise marketing spend.

Tech: React, TypeScript, Material UI, react-spring

EDUCATION

BSc Computer Science

University of Sunderland

2014 - 2018 (with industrial placement)



adam-mckenna@outlook.com +44 7404 895 383 Newcastle upon Tyne, UK

Programming Languages

JavaScript / TypeScript

PHP

Elixir

HTML

CSS / SASS

Core Technologies

Frontend: React, Vue, Angular

Backend: Node.js (Express,

Nest.js), Laravel

Tooling: Vite, Jest (testing)

DevOps: AWS

Other: TailwindCSS, A11y

Other Skills

Leadership

Pragmatism

Independence

UX/UI + service design

Languages

English (native)

German (basic)

Links

adammckenna.online
linkedin.com/in/adam-mckenna
github.com/adam-mckenna
dev.to/adammckenna